(rhythmic upbeat music)
♪ A little ditty about Jack and Diane ♪
♪ Two American kids growin'
up in the heartland ♪
♪ Jack, he's gonna be a football star ♪
♪ Diane's a debutante,
backseat of Jacky's car ♪
(rhythmic upbeat music continues)
♪ Suckin' on a chili dog
outside the Tastee-Freez ♪
♪ Diane's sittin' on Jacky's lap ♪
♪ He's got his hand between her knees ♪
♪ Jacky say, "Hey Diane, lets
run off behind a shady tree ♪
♪ Dribble off those Bobby Brooks slacks ♪
♪ Now do what I please," say uh ♪
♪ Oh yeah, life goes on ♪
♪ Long after the thrill
of livin' is gone ♪
♪ They say, oh yeah, life goes on ♪
♪ Long after the thrill
of livin' is gone ♪
♪ Now walk on ♪
(rhythmic upbeat music continues)
♪ Jacky sits back, collects
his thoughts for the moment ♪
♪ Scratches his head and
does his best James Dean ♪
♪ "Well then, there Diane, we
ought to run off to the city" ♪
♪ Diane says, "Baby, you
ain't missin' nothing" ♪
♪ And Jackie say, uh ♪
♪ Oh yeah, life goes on ♪
♪ Long after the thrill
of livin' is gone ♪
♪ Oh yeah, they say, life goes on ♪
♪ Long after the thrill
of livin' is gone ♪
(drums beating)
♪ So let it rock, let it roll ♪
♪ Let the Bible Belt
come and save my soul ♪
♪ Hold on to 16 as long as you can ♪
♪ Changes come around real soon ♪
♪ Make us women and men ♪
(drums beating continues)
(rhythmic upbeat music resumes)
♪ Oh yeah, life goes on ♪
♪ Long after the thrill
of livin' is gone ♪
♪ Oh yeah, they say life goes on ♪
♪ Long after the thrill
of livin' is gone ♪
♪ A little ditty 'bout Jack and Diane ♪
♪ Two American kids doin'
the best that they can ♪
(rhythmic upbeat music continues)